Bandera bombed Kherson for 8 years and Putin
бандеровцы бомбили 8 лет Херсон и Путин
started a special operation and therefore annexed
начал спецоперацию и поэтому присоединил
Kherson to Russia, like yes, he announced Well, yes, I
Херсон к России типа да объявил Ну да
understand, yes, it’s
понял да
interesting, yes Zelensky, I look at
Интересно да Зеленский я вот смотрите
how Zelensky is asking all sorts of
как Зеленский спрашиваю у всяких
Russian Federation Yes, how do you see
Российской Федерации Да как вы видите
the end of what for Russia should be the
окончание сво что для России должно быть
end of the special operation, the capture of Kiev  capture of
концом спецоперации взятие Киева взятие
Berlin capture of
Берлина взятие
Lvov
Львова
Volodya Hello What do you say
Володь Здравствуйте Ты что отвечайте
Volodya, I’m generally neutral about this Well,
Володь я к этому вообще нейтрально
you, as a person who
отношусь Ну вот ты как человек который
lives in Russia, this is how you would like
живёт в России вот как бы ты хотел чтобы
the special operation to end Friendship, well, like this
спецоперация Дружба ну как вот типа
Friendship that Russia takes and leaves
Дружба что Россия берёт и уходит из
Ukraine says it all Now
Украины полностью говорит всё Теперь
we’ll be friends, yes, but we’re not in
будем дружить да Так а мы же не в
Ukraine, I don’t know how everything happens there.
Украине я не знаю как там всё происходит
Yeah, for example, Ukraine says that
Ага вот например Украина говорит что
Russia is in Ukraine. Because Kherson,
Россия в Украине Потому что Херсон
Donetsk, Lugansk, Crimea is all Ukraine, well,
Донецк Луганск Крым - это всё Украина а
like Kherson. Oh, yes, Kherson region is there,
ну типа Херсон Ой да Херсон там область
we annexed it to us  Yes, well,
же мы присоединили к нам Да ну временно
they temporarily occupied part of Well, yes, Dada, time Kup,
оккупировали часть Ну да Дада врем Куп
because they were bombed, as far as I know,
потому что их бомбили насколько я знаю
Kherson
Херсон
was bombed, Well, yes, bombed, that is, I understand that you
бомбили Ну да бомби а то есть я понял вы
annexed Kherson because Ukraine
присоединили Херсон потому что Украина
Bombed
Бомбила
Kherson, Well, like, they temporarily occupied Or
Херсон Ну типа временно оккупировали Или
what is it because he said he’s
как это потому что н сказал для заты
starting a special  military operation and
начинает специальную военную операцию и
temporary occupation of Kherson Well, I don’t
временную оккупацию Херсона Так ну не не
know how everything was there. Exactly the same, yes, I can’t
знаю как там всё было Точно так да да не
say Well, because who is
могу сказать Ну потому что кто вот
Ukraine for 8 years Bombed Kherson and Putin
Украина 8 лет Бомбила Херсон и Путин
launched a special military operation to
начал специальную военную операцию по
protect Kherson Ukraine Why Ukraine is not
защиту Херсона Украина Почему Украину не
Ukrainian, all the people A  like
украинский же весь народ А типа
Bandera's Yes, yes, yes,
бандеровцы Да да да бандеровцы Да
Bandera's Yes, Bandera's bombed Kherson for 8 years and Putin
бандеровцы бомбили 8 лет Херсон и Путин
started a special operation and therefore annexed
начал спецоперацию и поэтому присоединил
Kherson to Russia, like yes, announced Well, yes, I
Херсон к России типа да объявил Ну да
understand, yes, it turns out
понял да
interesting, now Ukraine is
интересно получается вот сейчас Украина
already, I've been watching for the last year, yes,
уже я вот последний год точно смотрю да
last year I don't remember that Ukraine
последний год я не помню чтобы Украина
Bombed  Kherson, then if Ukraine is no longer
Бомбила Херсон то если уже Украина не
bombing Kherson, then maybe we should
бомбит Херсон то може уже надо
finish ours and give it back, well,
заканчивать свой и отдать назад ну
say All of you, since Kherson should not be bombed.
сказать Всё вы раз Херсон не бомбить Всё
We all defended Kherson and are leaving. Well, I don’t know about
мы защитили Херсон и уходим Ну я не знаю
you, it’s Vladimir Zelensky to all
у вас это Владимир Зеленский всем
the leadership. Well, Zelensky Zelensky gave
руководству Ну Зеленский Зеленский дал
instructions to these military that  We don’t bomb Kherson anymore,
указание этим военным что Херсон уже не
mini govo, we don’t bomb, over the last
мини гово мын не бомбим вот за последний
year no one can say a single time
год никто не может сказать ни одного ра
for Ukraine to bomb Kherson like the
чтобы Украина Бомбила Херсон как
previous 8
предыдущие 8
years. I can’t even say what
лет Я не могу сказать даже что будет
will happen next. I can’t even guess what will happen next. I don’t
предположить что будет дальше не я не
want to guess.  I want you to see
хочу предполагать Я хочу как ты видишь
what needs to be done, I myself don’t even see
что нужно сделать я я сам даже не вижу
like
типа
Yago Ukraine is bombing Kherson Yes, and I started my own
яго Украина бомбит Херсон Да и начал сво
defense of Kherson, now I’m looking at the
по защите Херсона то сейчас я смотрю
last year Russia is bombing Kherson
последний год Россия бомбит Херсон
Ukraine is now in Kherson Yes, and Russia
Украина сейчас в Херсоне Да а Россия
is bombing Kherson, killing people in Kherson, that
бомбит Херсон убивает людей в Херсоне то
is  Putin started a special operation to protect
есть Путин начал спецоперацию по защите
Kherson, yes, because
Херсона да потому потому что 8 лет
Kherson was bombed for 8 years, but now Putin is bombing
бомбили Херсон но теперь Путин бомбит
Kherson didn’t understand anything at all. Well, everything is
Херсон вообще ничего не понял Ну всё
complicated. I myself didn’t understand anything. Well, yes, there’s a
сложно Я сам ничего не понял Ну да тут
complex scheme, damn it, everything is so confusing in this politics,
сложная схема блин в этой политике всё
and you’re a bit of a politician,
а вы что политик немножко
yes?  something else you are interested in is
да А ещё чем увлекаетесь так
programming, that is, a computer scientist, too,
программирование то есть информатик тоже
too And you are a computer
ро тоже А вы
scientist, who are you? You said a computer
информатик кто Вы Вы сказали информатик
scientist, too, in your own way. Well, I meant that you are a computer scientist, in your own way. Yes,
вы информатик в своём роде Да я в свом
I am an informatician, in my own way.
информа Я спортсмен в свом ро ком
I understood And this is like
лыжник понял А это типа как лыжные
just ski racing or there are some kind of tricks that
просто гонки или там какие-то трюки что
ski racing jumps high from a springboard And I understood because it looks like this is
лыжные гонки А понял потому что похоже
how you jump from a springboard Well, I’m
вот как с трамплина прыгаешь Ну что
very high, I’m running lodges running Yes And
очень высоко я беговые лож беговые Да А
when you run, you run in open
вы когда бегаете вы бегаете на открытой
areas or  somewhere among the trees there,
местности или где-то среди деревьев там
too Well, it happens, no, in the open, rarely
тоже Ну бывает нет на открытые редко
like Among the trees in the forest Well, there is a
типа Среди деревьев по лесу Ну
special track for this, and that is, there is a
специальна трасса для этого а то есть
special track that doesn’t happen when
специальная трасса не бывает такое что
you drive and at speed you can fly into a
едешь и на скорости можно влететь в
tree, that doesn’t
дерево такого не
happen No, well, it’s someone who doesn’t know how to drive  But
бывает Нет ну это кто не умеет ездить Но
usually this is all provided for in the snow.
обычно это всё предусмотрено и по снегу
Well, Buran there is
Ну Буран там
a snowmobile. Well, in your history there
снегоход Ну в твоей истории спортивное
was a sports event where you crashed into
случалось тако что ты врезался в
some kind of
какие-то
obstacles,
заграждения
but there is no such thing as a sharp 90-degree turn
нет но неже поворота на 90 граду резкого
from the descent, I understand that this did not
со спуска такого нет понял такого не
happen,
было
yes in my history there was a maximum
да в моей истории было максимальная
speed  90 km HF But this is in the
скорость 90 км ВЧ Но это
Summer In the summer on skis that are on wheels yes Uh-huh
Летом Летом на лыжах которые на колёсах
Cool Well, imagine 90 km per
Угу Прикольно Ну представь себе 90 км в
hour from the
час со
descent like on asphalt like going down Yes it
спуска так на асфальте типа спускался Да
was in this Buturlinovka this is, in
это было в этом Бутурлиновка это
my opinion, the Voronezh region And the cars
по-моему Воронежской область А машины
What were they doing at that moment
Что делали в этот момент
and the track  conveyed And this
а трассу передали А это соревнования
was also a competition, yes, the
тоже были
Russian championship, I understood And you, this
да чемпионат России понял А ты вот это
summer on the asphalt, like, well, it never
летом на асфальте типа никогда не ну не
happened that I fell there. Hey, it
было тако что там упал Слышь
was interesting how this
было интересно как это
happens, I’m not at speed, like not at
происходит я не на скорости типа не на
high speed. Well, I see. Well, it’s not at
высокой скорости Ну я вижу Да что не на
high speed.  but Explain how it happened
высокой но а Объясни как это случилось
Well, in short, a stone fell under a wheel of
Ну камень короче попал вот под колесо
crushed stone. So immediately, bam, your leg
щебёнка Вот и сразу бац нога раз
turned out once and you fell. And how did you fall on
вывернулся и падаешь А как ты упал на
what, well,
что ну
grouping to save roads is an expensive thing.
сгруппировав спасти дороги дорогая штука
That is, when you fall, you save
То есть ты когда падаешь ты спасаешь
sticks and not your head, it turns out
палки а не голову получается
[laughter]
[смех]
Yes,
да
like, you’ll break your head, I don’t care, but the
типа башку разобьёшь пофиг замотать а
poles are
палки
expensive. Well, the poles are the first thing I
дорогие Да ну палки в первую очередь
save. And on the head we have
спасаю А на главе у нас
a helmet
шлем
and how much do the poles cost? Well, my
а сколько палки стоят Ну у меня
professional ones cost 30,000 rubles, 300
профессиональные стоят 30.000 руб 300
dollars. Yes, for a pole or for two poles, for
долларов Да за палку или за две палки за
two poles. That is, it turns out you when
две палки То есть получается ты когда
you're going, you're
едешь ты
afraid, you've
боишься сломал А таких палок штук 10
broken it, and you've already broken about 10 of these poles, that is, you can imagine
сломал уже то есть представляешь что ты
that you're walking. In short, you have 30,000 rubles in your hands, 300 dollars, and you're falling, and instead of thinking about how not to break your head,
того чтобы думать как не разбить башку
you're thinking, Well, how can you damn well avoid
ты короче думаешь Ну как короче блин Э
crushing these?
не помять эти
bucks Well, no, there’s no such thing in the head Well, like
баксы Ну нет такого нет в голове Ну типа
you fall on your shoulder on a soft place and you
падаешь на плечо там на мягкое место а
can’t break your head there at
голову там никак не разобьёшь на
low speed the nose can be broken, no
маленькой скорости нос можно разбить не
wonder if you’re at high
не понятное дело если ты на большой
speed you don’t think about any sticks
скорости ты никаких палках не думаешь
like you’re resting on your hand on your leg
типа ты там на руку на ногу упирается
it’s like that, if you actually
она такое если ты прям вообще было
just fell on roller skates on the classic ones,
просто упал на роллерах на классических
these are the ones that go like this, well, like
это которые вот так вот идут ну вот
that with two feet forward, I understood yes Well, you
так двумя ногами вперёд понял да Ну ты
know the classic skate move Yes, the
знаеш коньковый классический ход Да
skate move is like that to
коньковый вот так в
the sides, but on classic roller skates the
стороны вот а на классических роллерах
rear wheel does not go back shorter  That
заднее колесо назад не едет короче То
is, I was just driving forward, then I
есть что вперёд только ехал потом
pushed, I stood on them, they drove away from under me
толкнул стоял на них они из-под меня
and didn’t go back, and just fell like that; in short, it’s
уехали а назад не едут и вот прямо вот
cool, interesting, but for example, well,
прикольно интересно а вот например э вот
if you valued your body parts in
если бы ты оценивал свои части тела в
dollars or rubles, how much would you  I would
доллара или в рублях сколько бы ты бы
rate the
Оценил
head, damn, I
голову
can’t say Well, that’s about it Well, there’s
м бля не могу сказать Ну примерно Вот
a lot of [ __ ] Well,
вот и до Ну [__] очень много Ну
for example
например
Well, 100 million rubles 100 million rubles that
Ну 100 млн рублей 100 млн рублей это
turns out to be a million bucks for the
получается миллион баксов за
head Yes, I understand And the right
башку Да понял А правую
hand is the right
руку правую
hand Well, also understand the right ru is smaller, it’s
руку Ну также понь право ру поменьше она
cheaper than doge without  head, you can’t survive this
дешевле дож без башки же не выживешь сей
without your right hand, you can Well, without your right hand
без правой руки можно Ну без правой руки
you can Well, 80 Well, okay, 5,000
можно Ну ладно 80 Ну ладно 5.000
dollars 65,000 dollars for the right hand
долларов 65.000 долларов за правую руку
dadada That is, if those if someone
дадада То есть если те если кто-то тебе
gave you 70 grand bucks, would you give your
70 штук баксов приложил ты бы отдал
right
правую
hand no now one hundred and 65 million  rubles
руку нет сейчас сто 65 миллионов рублей
it turns out to be
это
650 Now
650 Сейчас
stand Yarik where At the game at the
стой Ярик где На игре на
game And
игре А
this is Good night Turn on the light
это Спокойной ночи Включите свет
please I need you I’ll turn it off myself
пожалуйста я тебе надо я выключу сам
okay it’s That Mom didn’t come to us in the
ладно это Что Мамка приходила не мы в
dorm But in general this is a ski dorm of
общаге А в общ это лыжная общага
some kind not this is generally slightly sporty
какая-то не это вообще спортивная слегка
and hockey players  and this is like the watchman walks
и хоккеисты а это типа вахтёрша ходит
around, like, goes to bed in the
всех типа ложит спать в дев
maiden: And the teacher, like, at 10 o’clock
в: А воспиталка типа вот в 10 часов
lights out there, everyone
отбой там все дела
understands Like, yes, so that they fight back in short, yes, I understand,
понял Типа да чтобы отбивались короче да
yes And look well, and this is a question
понял да А смотри хорошо а такой вопрос
like hand 165 And for example,
вот типа рука 165 А например яйцо
how much would you value an egg  no Well, listen, I
сколько ты оценил бы не Ну слушай даже
don’t even want to think about it, but I was thinking about my hand, and I was thinking about my
не хочу думать про это а про руку думал
hand, about my head, I was thinking about an egg, no, I don’t know, there’s just
да про руку про башку думал яйцо не я не
nothing to do. I’m
знаю просто делать нечего Я
also a little under the weather for them. And you were
вот тоже им немножко поде дирола А ты в
n’t in any competitions abroad, well, they closed Russia
соревнованиях нету ну Россию же закрыли
like I mean they closed Well, ours don’t compete
типа В смысле закрыли Ну не выступают
anywhere at international events now because of
наши ну уже сейчас нигде на
something from the war But it’s cool I didn’t know, that
чего из войны А прикольно Я не знал то
is, it turns out they don’t let you into
есть получается вас не пускают на
some international competitions
какие-то международные соревнования
Well, yes, well they let you in Well, you know, it’s not all about
Ну да ну пускает Ну знаете вы вс не на я
sports at all  I don’t look, I don’t
спорт вообще не смотрю я не
understand Not under the Russian flag, but
понимаю Не под российским флагом а
the athletes, roughly speaking, there is a white flag,
спортсмены грубо говоря там белый флаг
in short, they give up the white flag Yes, well, like,
короче сдаются белый флаг Да ну типа
people who are
люди кто
promising play, but oh, why
перспективные играют но
don’t you play like that under the white
о а что ты не играешь так само под белым
flag abroad
флагом за границей
Like, I’m not that professional an
Типа так я не настолько профессиональный
athlete And I understand  you just live there anyway
спортсмен А понял ты просто там вообще
Ponya Okay, well, I’m a master of sports,
аги пожить Поня Окей ну я мастер спорта
of course, but Well, I see a master, yes, you know.
конечно но Ну я вижу мастер да понимаешь
And who will need to live there? Cyber ​​master,
А кем надо будет жить там Кибер мастером
who do you need to be in order to
кем надо быть чтобы уже за границей
perform abroad? Well, at least an Honored
выступать Ну как минимум заслуженным
Master of Sports, an Honored Mas And to
мастером спорта заслуженным мас А чтобы
deserve it, you need to win  some kind of
заслуженно это надо выиграть какой-то
championship yes Yeah Not only the championship I
чемпионат да Угу Не только чемпионат я
sing like that What is deservedly given for
так пою Что заслуженного дают за
international championships deservedly
международные чемпионаты заслуженного
deserved for what is
заслуженного за что
given The Olympic Games of international affairs are
дают Олимпийские игры международника
given The Olympic Games
дают Олимпийские игры
are given And yes it is deservedly given for the Olympic
дают А да заслуженно это за Олимпийские
Games of sports if you win Yes and the
игры спорта если ты выиграешь Да и
World Championship it turns out now
чемпионат мира то получается теперь
look you  you can’t go abroad there
смотри ты не можешь поехать там за
under the white flag because you are
границу под белым флагом потому что ты
not an Honored Master of Sports, but an
не заслуженный мастер спорта а
Honored One, because the Honored Ones give the
заслуженным потому что заслуженные дают
International World Championship for the Olympic Games,
за Олимпийские игры международный
Master of Sports, then International Master of Sports, then
мира мастер спорта потом международный
Honored Master of Sports, so
мастер спорта потом заслуженный вот
in order to complete the International Master of
чтобы выполнить международный Мастер
Sports, you need to go
спорт нужно ехать
to that, but they’re
на
not allowed there
вот а туда не пускают международника вот
In Russia, they say, you can also
на России говорят тоже можно
do international work, you can do it
выполнить международника можно выполнить
in Russia, but what you deserve only at the
на России а вот заслуженного только на
Olympics is given by Che, and what city do
Олимпиаде даёт и Че а это в каком городе
you live in, like skiers? Yes, all over Russia
Вы живёте типа лыжники Да по всей России
we are skiers. Well, now this is
мы лыжники Ну вот сейчас вот
where we are now in Penza, you’re like on
где мы сейчас в Пензе это вы типа на
some training camp just arrived Well, yes And
сборы какие-то приехали просто Ну да А
I’m still thinking like how is it in Penza like I
всё я думаю типа как это де в Пензе типа
think there’s a super
думаю что там в Пензе супершкола
ski school in Penza And what city do you live in? I’m the city of
лыж А вы в каком городе живёте я город
Khmelnitsky And wow I
Хмельницкий А ничего
hear And what about 300,000 population I don’t
себе слу А как ну 300.000 население Я не
know small not small  Why are you
знаю маленький не маленький А вы что
streaming? Yes, I’m a Streamer. Wow.
стрими стримлю Да я Стример А ничего
Cool. Well, that’s how I communicate. I don’t
себе Прикольно Ну я так общаюсь Я не
quarrel with Russians. Why are there a lot of you
ссорюсь с россиянами А что много вас
watching now? There are not enough subscribers, 2725
сейчас смотрят подписчиков мало 2725
so far. Well, hello everyone, then I’m not
пока Ну Всем привет тогда меня там не
like that, because I’m a Russian there, well, no, well, you’re
как то что я там россиянин ну не ну ты
not  about politics you see you don’t
же не про политику видишь ты не
quarrel So about life about sports
ссоришься Так что так о жизни о спорте
I was interested I didn’t
мне интересно было я наме лыжах не
understand skiing there I was interested I’ll go and
разбирался там мне интересно было зайду
look at something channel What is the name of
посмотрю по что-что канал Как называется
where in the yubbe Andrey popk
где в юбе Андрей
Andrey as well Andrey in Russian
попк Андрей как ну Андрей по-русски
Andrey popk popk yes  popk yes Andriy popk
Андрей попк попк да попк да Андрий попк
uh-huh, but your dorms look like
угу а а у вас вот общаги типа получается
sports ones, they look like what year they
спортивные они типа какого года
were built? Come on, show me the ran Yes,
постройки нашёл Да ну-ка покажи ран
hello
Да привет
hello. You have dorms, what year they were
привет У вас общаги какого года
built, they turn out to be sports ones? Oh, I
постройки получается спортивные О я даже
can’t even
не могу
say that yet Under the Union somewhere
сказать это ещё При Союзе где-то
were under construction Yes to all subscribers Hello
строились Да всем подписчикам Привет
everyone Then for the pluses so that there
всем Потом под плюсики чтобы активность
is activity, I’m just wondering how I am
была вот мне просто интересно как я
when I meet our students or
когда встречаю наших студентов или
some athletes, I ask them to
каких-то спортсменов я прошу чтобы они
show how life is in student
показали как вот быт в студенческих
dormitories, can you show how you,
общежитиях можешь показать как у вас
like, in Russian
типа в российских
dormitories, everything is arranged [ __ ]  Well,
общежитиях обустроено всё Бля ну
now switch the camera Yes, just like that or
сейчас камеру то переключить Да просто
so on in our room like this is the
так у на у нас в комнате типа вот
room Yes, everything is in the room and here is
комната Да всё в комнате
the push here everything is going on here you have a
ти вот толчок тут все дела вот у вас
clean normal repairman there is this is not a
чистенько нормально ремонтик есть это не
soviet taka super not normal everything
совковая така супер не нормально всё
in general, well, athletes are respected
вообще в принципе ну спортсменов уважают
Because there is such a thing that like after
Потому что есть такое что типа посля
like there are still old walls no no no we have
типа ещё старые стены нене не у нас
such a new girl
такая новенькая
hugged And you were in Crimea at
обнял А ты в Крыму был на соревнованиях
some kind of competition or
каких-то или на
training camp No you weren’t And what about Crimea Don’t
сборах Нет не был А что в Крым Не
[music]
[музыка]
go I don’t know it doesn’t take place in Sochi
ездите не знаю не проходит в Сочи вот
went to Crimea, they don’t do it either, I don’t think I
ездили в Крыму не проводят тоже вроде не
know Well, we still have a winter sport
знаю Ну у нас всё-таки зимний вид спорта
Well, if about skiing in Crimea, just
к Ну это если о на лыже в Крыму как раз
90 km/h you can go skiing in
90 кмч на лыжах можно покататься
the summer Dangerous with apet like
летом Опасно с апет вот
that Yeah yeah
так
Okay, let’s run,
Угу да Хорошо давай побегу
subscribe to Mi Telegram  right now the axis of
подпишись на Mi Telegram прямо зараз ось
wine and
вин а
popk is even more and more respectful
попк це дуже и дуже важливо
L
L